Guide to the Cornell University Office of the Registrar miscellany, 1913-1968,
Cornell University Office of the Registrar miscellany, 1913-1968.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Office of the Registrar miscellany, 1913-1968, 1962-1968 (bulk)
36-1-876
Cornell University. Office of the Registrar.
.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, annual reports, and printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes a summary of both undergraduate and graduate annual degree awards from the first commencement in 1869 to 1966 and annual fall enrollment statistics (1868-1968) compiled by Registrar Herbert H. Williams; correspondence (1963-64) between Williams, Cornell President James A. Perkins, and Elwood Hunter of Josten's-E.A. Wright Company of Philadelphia, diploma suppliers, concerning planning and preparation of the new form of diploma, 1963-64, Williams' report (1963) to the Ad Hoc Diploma Revision Committee, and twelve sample diplomas; a letter and postcard from David F. Hoy, 1919; and annual reports of the registrar (1962-68).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes a summary of both undergraduate and graduate annual degree awards from the first commencement in 1869 to 1966 and annual fall enrollment statistics (1868-1968) compiled by Registrar Herbert H. Williams; correspondence (1963-64) between Williams, Cornell President James A. Perkins, and Elwood Hunter of Josten's-E.A. Wright Company of Philadelphia, diploma suppliers, concerning planning and preparation of the new form of diploma, 1963-64, Williams' report (1963) to the Ad Hoc Diploma Revision Committee, and twelve sample diplomas; a letter and postcard from David F. Hoy, 1919; and annual reports of the registrar (1962-68).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Office of the Registrar.; Hoy, David F.; Hunter, Ellwood.; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-; Williams, Herbert H.; Cornell University--Degrees.; Cornell University--Statistics.
Subjects:
Degrees, Academic.
Form and Genre Terms:
Diplomas.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Annual report of the registrar, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual report of the registrar, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual report of the registrar, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual report of the registrar, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual report of the registrar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual report of the registrar, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence regarding the selection of a new design for the Cornell diploma, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Summary of annual degree awards, 1869 to present, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Annual fall enrollment records, 1868 to present, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Letter from Registrar David F. Hoy, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Application for admission to courses, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Explanation of grading systems, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Diploma and twelve samples of the new diploma adopted in Spring 1964 (oversized material), 1963-1964